this really good measure of distances
can of course enter the iun or
something to measure out also to is
the edge of the forest and stuff, but here you can
take some benchmarks and then sort of lay
up a plan to about this far there
can i take the shot and yes you build up
a sort of ready-made plan as you have it
that you can't help but think about it
When the game comes, you know it
for example over there Eh that timber
the pile so Yes here [ __ ] by what one has
you create benchmarks, that's me
do when I come out to sessions like this
there is longer
distance he comes over the wall think
I Yes, it was too fast, completely impossible
I just heard on the radio that
Alexander has managed to hta again damn well
fun lovely recordings
I have slapped others a lot